(Amy:)Sheldon, sometimes people seek the comfort
of physical contact in moments like this.
(Sheldon:)I am not flying back to Texas
just so my mom can give me a hug.
(Amy:)Okay. Well, what I think is going on here...
(Amy:)...is you have a pathological need
for closure.
(Sheldon:)Oh. That's nonsense.
(Sheldon:)You tell me stories about your day
all the time. I don't care how they end.
(Amy:)You know, I might be able
to help you with this.
There's a field of behavioral neuroscience
that examines...
(Amy:)...ways to retrain your neural pathways
so stuff like this bothers you less.
(Sheldon:)But I just told you,
I don't have a problem with closure.
- You sure about that?
- Quite sure.